HERE Locals files 6199/004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
HERE Locals files
1982-1995
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Hotel Employees & Restaurant Employees International Union
6199/004
8 cubic feet
8 linear ft.
Records.
8254417
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 04, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 21, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: All 6199 Collections
Hotel Employees & Restaurant Employees International Union; UNITE HERE (Organization)
8254417
- Local 509 Monthly Reports, 1987-1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Local 509, Anaconda, Montana. International Trusteeship, 1987-1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Local 806. Deer Lodge, Montana, 1978-1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Local 806. Deer Lodge, Montana, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Local 806, Deer Lodge, Montana, Monthly Reports, 1988-1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Local 806, Deer Lodge, Montana. International Trusteeship, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Local 21-s, New York, 1984-1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Local 18-s New York, 1984-1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Local 42-s, New York, 1985-1991 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Local 106-s, New York, 1984-1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Local 719-s, New York, 1984-1991 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- By laws, Local 465, 1974-1987 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Local 465, General President Correspondence, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Local 465 General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Local 465 Form LM-3 File, 1986-1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- By Laws, Local 570, General President, 1966-1990 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Local 570 General President Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Local 570 General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Local 570 Form LM-3, 1984-1990 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- By Laws, Local 657, 1982-1990 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Local 657 General President Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Local 657 General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Local 657 LM/990 File, 1985-1990 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Local 657 Roster, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Scope and Contents
  April 1 1989
- By Laws, Local 741, General President, 1971-1990 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Local 741 General President Correspondence, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- By Laws, Local 746, General President, 1977-1990 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Local 746, General President Trusteeship Reports, 1986-1990 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Local 741 General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Local 741 LM/990 File, 1984-1990 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Local 741 Roster, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Local 746. International Trusteeship, 1986-1991 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Local 746 General President Correspondence, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Local 746, General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1986-1991 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Local 746, LM/990 File, 1984-1991 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Local 746 Roster, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  August 1986
- Joint Executive Board, Anchorage, Alaska. By Laws, 1962-1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Joint Executive Board, Anchorage, Alaska. General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1982-1990 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Local 50, Hayward, California, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  February 3 1992
- Local 50 Monthly Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Local 50, Hayward, California, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Local 50, Hayward, California, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Local 50, Hayward, California, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Local 815-s, New York Jurisdiction, 1984-1994 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Local 815-s, New York, Current, 1986-1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Local 745-s, New York, Jurisdiction (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Local 517-s, New York, Current, 1984-1992 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Local 517-s, New York, Jurisdiction, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Local 106-s, Production Service and Sales Council, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Local 28 Oakland, California, 1975-1994 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Local 28, Oakland, California, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Local 28, Oakland, California, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Local 15 Southern, Illinois, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Local 15, Southern, Illinois, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Local 15, Southern, Illinois, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Local 767, Regina, Saskatchewan, Canada, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Local 767, Regina, Saskatchewan, Canada, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Local 636, Prince Rupert, British Columbia, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Local 636, Prince Rupert, British Columbia, Canada, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Local 533, Helena, Montana, 1979-1993 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Local 533, Helena, Montana, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Local 281, Paducah, Kentucky, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Local 281, Paducah, Kentucky, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Local 281, Paducah, Kentucky Jurisdiction, 1961-1993 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Local 300-s, New York Jurisdiction, 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Local 300-s, New York, Current, 1984-1991 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Local 222-s, New York Jurisdiction, 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Local 222-s, New York Current, 1985-1993 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Local 422-s, New York Current, 1984-1992 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Local 422-s, New York Jurisdiction, 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  In Spanish and English
- Records of Local Rosters and Miscellaneous Papers, 1959-1978 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  Bound book
- 1115 Hospital and Service Employees Union Miscellaneous, 1992-1994 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Production, Service and Sales District Council, 1974-1985 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- International Production, Service and Sales Employee Union Merger, 1984-1994 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Production, Service and Sales District Council Jurisdiction, 1982-1987 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Production, Service and Sales District Council Current, 1990-1994 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- International Production, Service and Sales Employee Union District Council Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Production, Service and Sales District Council Current, 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Local 21-s, New York Jurisdiction, 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Hearing in the Matter of the Trusteeship of the HERE Union Local 70, Columbus and Dayton Ohio, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  June 16 1993
- Trusteeship of Local 70, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Trusteeship of Local 70, Jonas B Katz, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- 1115 District Council, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  February 1 1992
- Local 886 Monthly Reports, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Local 886, Birmingham, Alabama Trusteeship, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  June 1 1992
- Local 886, Birmingham, Alabama, 1968-1994 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Local 886, Birmingham, Alabama, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Local 886, Birmingham, Alabama, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Local 777, Windsor, Ontario, New Local International Trusteeship, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  April 181994
- Local 727, Maryville, Tennessee, 1984-1994 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Local 727 Maryville, Tennessee, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Local 727, Maryville, Tennessee, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Local 50, Hayward, California, 1992-1994 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Stephen Skaggs, Local 70 Appeal, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Local 541, Pascagoula, Mississippi, 1979-1994 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Local 541, Pascagoula, Mississippi, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Local 541, Pascagoula, Mississippi, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- By Laws for the Joint Council of Dining Car Employees, 1957-1990 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Joint Council Dining Car Employees, 1948-1967 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Dining Car Employees Chicago, see General President Correspondence Part 1, 1962-1983 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Dining Car Employees Chicago, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- By Laws, Local 810, 1965-1988 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Local 810, General President Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Local 810 General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Local 810 LM-3/990 File, 1984-1992 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- By Laws, Local 495, 1976-1991 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Local 495 General President Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Local 495 General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Local 495 LM-3/990 File, 1984-1991 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- By Laws, Local 336, 1962-1985 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Local 336, General President Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Local 336 General Secretary-Treasurer, 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Local 336 LM-3/990 File, 1984-1991 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- By Laws, Local 267, General President, 1974-1981 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Local 267 General President Correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Local 267 General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Local 267 LM-3/990 File, 1985-1991 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Local 267 Roster, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  December 1 1990
- By Laws, Local 136 General President, 1955-1987 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Local 136 General President Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Local 136 General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Local 136 LM-3/990 File, 1984-1991 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- By Laws, Local 123 General President, 1959-1990 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Local 123, General President Correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Local 1230 General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Local 123 LM-3/990 File, 1984-1991 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Bylaws Local 88, General President, 1984-1992 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Local 88 General President Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Local 70, Columbus and Dayton Ohio, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1983-1993 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Local 70, Columbus, Ohio, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Local 70, Monthly Reports, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  May 3 1993
- Local 70, Columbus and Dayton Ohio, Indianapolis Indiana Trusteeship, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  May 3 1995
- Dining Car Employees Chicago, 1987-1991 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  See General President Correspondence Part 3
- Dining Car Employees Joint Council Trusteeship, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  General President; May 1 1990
- Joint Council Monthly Reports, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Joint Council Dining Car Employees, General Secretary Treasurer, 1982-1989 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Local 26, Rapid City, South Dakota, 1977-1991 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Local 46, Rapid City, South Dakota, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Local 220, Eureka, California, 1978-1992 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Local 220, Eureka, California, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Local 509, Anaconda, Montana, 1973-1992 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Local 509, Anaconda, Montana, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Local 23, By Laws, 1984-1988 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Local 23 General President General Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Local 23 Miscellaneous Documents Regarding Finances, Colonial Williamsburg, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Merger of Local 23 into Local 32, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Local 23Loan Repayment, Norfolk, Virginia, 1979-1983 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  General Secretary-Treasurer
- Local 23, Loan Repayment $2,500, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  March 1 1983 - June 8 1984
- Local 23 General Secretary Treasurer Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Local 23 LM-3/990 File, 1984-1990 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Local 83 By-Laws, 1978-1986 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Local 83, Russell, Kentucky, General President Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Local 83 Roster, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  January 1 1988
- Loan Repayment, Local 83, Russell Kentucky, 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Local 83, General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Local 83, LM-3/990 File, 1984-1990 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Local 134 Bylaws, 1969-1980 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Local 134 Jurisdiction, 1959-1989 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Local 134 Correspondence General President, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Local 134 General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Local 134 LM-3/990 File, 1984-1990 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Local 163 McKeesport, Pennsylvania, 1964-1984 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- By Laws, Local 279 General President, 1960-1981 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Local 279 General President Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Local 279 General Secretary-Treasurer, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Local 279 LM-3/990 File, 1984-1991 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Local 279 Roster, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  September 1 1987
- By Laws Local 298 General President, 1948-1983 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  Contains maps
- Local 298, General President Correspondence, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Local 298 Loan Details, 1985-1990 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Local 298 General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Local 298 Monthly Per Capita Tax Report, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  November 1983
- Local 298 LM-3/990 File, 1984-1990 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Local 397 Bylaws, 1959-1990 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Local 397 Jurisdiction, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Local 397, Harrisburg, Pennsylvania International Trusteeship, 1985-1990 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Local 397, Harrisburg, Pennsylvania, International Trusteeship File 2, 1985-1990 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Local 397, General President Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Local 397, Monthly Reports Trusteeship, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Local 397 General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Local 397 Roster, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  February 1 1988; restricted
- Local 397 LM-3/990 File, 1984-1990 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Bylaws, Local 417, 1979-1987 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Local 417, General President Correspondence, 1985-1990 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Local 417 General Secretary-Treasurer, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Local 417 LM-3/990 File, 1984-1990 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Local 417 Roster, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Death and Defense Funds for Locals 1 - 54, 1902-1940 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Death and Defense Funds for Locals 55 - 100, 1902-1939 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Death and Defense Funds for Locals 101 - 150, 1902-1939 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Death and Defense Funds for Locals 151-200, 1902-1939 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Death and Defense Funds for Locals 201 - 250, 1902-1939 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Death and Defense Funds for Locals 251 - 300, 1902-1939 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Death and Defense Funds for Locals 301 - 342, 1902-1939 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Death and Defense Funds for Locals 343 - 380, 1902-1939 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Death and Defense Funds for Locals 381 - 415, 1905-1939 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Death and Defense Funds for Locals 416 - 460, 1902-1939 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Death and Defense Funds for Locals 461 - 500, 1902-1939 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Death and Defense Funds for Locals 501-535, 1903-1939 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Death and Defense Funds for Locals 536-575, 1903-1941 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Death and Defense Funds for Locals 576 - 610, 1903-1939 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Death and Defense Funds for Locals 611 - 650, 1903-1939 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Death and Defense Funds for Locals 651 - 685, 1903-1939 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Death and Defense Funds for Locals 686 - 715, 1903-1939 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Death and Defense Funds for Locals 716 - 750, 1903-1939 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Death and Defense Funds for Locals 751 - 790, 1903-1939 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Death and Defense Funds for Locals 791 - 830, 1904-1939 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Death and Defense Funds for Locals 831 - 1000, 1905-1939 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Death and Defense Funds for Locals 1926 - 1941, 1904-1941 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Local Unions by State, 1908-1919 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  Handwritten cards
- Bylaws Local 340, 1954-1977 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Bylaws Local 360, 1977-1982 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Bylaws Local 442, 1979-1983 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Bylaws Local 446, 1973-1982 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Bylaws Local 483, 1973-1983 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Bylaws Local 517, 1978-1984 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Bylaws Local 533, 1981-1984 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Bylaws Local 550, 1980-1988 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Bylaws Local 631, 1971-1982 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Bylaws Local 681, 1981-1983 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Bylaws Local 688, 1982-1986 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Bylaws Local 719, 1964-1987 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Bylaws Local 737, 1976-1981 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Bylaws Local 767, 1966-1976 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Bylaws Local 775, 1965-1970 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Bylaws Local 791, 1976-1983 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Bylaws Local 804, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Bylaws Local 814, 1961-1984 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Bylaws Local 868, 1965-1979 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Bylaws Local 879, 1965-1981 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Bylaws, Ohio State Council, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Bylaws, Pennsylvania State Council, 1985-1988 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Local 1, Chicago, Illinois, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Contains one photograph, of a woman at a desk.
- Local 2, San Francisco, California, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Local 2 "Action Reporter" Periodicals, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  San Francisco, California
- Local 5, Honolulu, Hawaii, 1982-1988 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Contains one photograph
- Local 5, Honolulu, Hawaii, Periodicals, 1982-1990 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Local 6, New York, New York, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  Contains 2 photographs and multiple photocopies of newspapers
- Local 6, New York Hotel Strike, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  Contains 5 photographs; in English and French
- Local 6 New York, Assorted Hotel Strike Periodicals, 1984-1987 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Local 8, Seattle, Washington, 1980-1984 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Local 9, Portland, Oregon, 1982-1989 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Local 11, Los Angeles, California, 1980-1983 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  In English and Spanish
- Local 12, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Local 16, Central Illinois, 1981-1983 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Local 19, San Jose, California Periodicals, 1980-1983 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Local 24, Detroit, Michigan, Periodicals and Reviews, 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Local 24, "Hotel, Bar and Restaurant Review" Periodicals, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Local 25, Washington, DC, 1980-1984 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  Contains 7 photographs
- Local 26, Boston, Massachusetts, 1980-1990 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Local 26, Boston, Massachusetts, "Local 26 Unity" Newspaper, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Local 30, San Diego, California, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Local 34, New Haven, Connecticut, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Local 40, Vancouver, British Columbia, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Local 40, Vancouver, British Columbia, "The Mixer" Newspaper, 1980-1984 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Local 49, Sacramento, California Newsletters, 1980-1984 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Local54, Atlantic City, New Jersey "Tips" Newspaper, 1981-1983 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Local 75, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Local 88, Ontario, Canada, 1986-1990 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Local 100, New York (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Local 165, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  Contains "Union Again Las Vegas" pin
- Local 226, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1980-1990 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Local 261, Ottawa, Ontario, Canada, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Local 274, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1958-1980 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Local 828, No Location Newsletters, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Local 847 or 775, No Location (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Local 878, Anchorage, Alaska Newsletters, 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 35)